Dima Tolmachev

Software developer

Details

Currently located in Georgia

Phone:

+995 599 00 49 19

Email:

dima.tolmachev@outlook.com

Telegram:

@dimatolmachev

Personal site:

https://dimatolmachev.me/

Skills

- TypeScript
- React.js / Next.js
- Node.js, express.js
- Python, Flask
- PostgreSQL / non-relational DBs
- Linux OS
- Git
- Docker

Soft skills

- Analytical skills
- Problem solving
- Attention to detail
- Work ethic
- Adaptability

Languages

- Russian, native
- English, upper-intermediate
- Czech, intermediate

References

Nikita Gorbukhov from Metrica Agency

> Telegram: @nikitabmx Email: nekitenzo@gmail.com

Tolmachev Alexey from Legion-it

> Telegram: @BA_Aleksey Email: gregorthedark@gmail.com

Profile

Young and talented software developer with a history of leading IT projects and engineering different types of web services.

I was both employed and worked on my own projects. I also have an experience of over 3 years of commercial development.

I am looking for a challenging position that will allow me to fulfil my potential and contribute to my future employer's success.

Experience

I am positioning myself as a web developer, mainly frontend. The main programming languages I use are TypeScript & JavaScript (ES6 specification). I have experience with a wide range of different frameworks. I am keen about new technologies, but my main stack is Express JS for server-side development and React JS for SPA frontend.

Employment history

Full-stack developer at Metrica Agency, Moscow, Russia May 2022 – Present

Responsibilities:

- 1. Development SPA & SSR applications
- 2. Writing customized unit tests
- 3. Code reviews

Technology stack:

- Typescript
- Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB
- React.js + Next.js, Mobx

Developer at Tokenizer, Moscow, Russia

January 2022 – August 2022

Responsibilities:

- 1. Scaling desktop application for automated checkouts on ecommerce sites and NFT minting
- 2. Writing technical documentation

Technology stack:

- JavaScript and Python metaprogramming
- RPC interaction: Ethereum, Solana, Cardano

Team leader & developer at Quasar Alpha Group, Moscow, Russia

September 2021 – May 2022

Responsibilities:

- 1. Maintaining and scaling the renewal subscription system (recurring payments in cryptocurrency)
- 2. Communication with customers and developing project roadmap according to their desires
- 3. Team management, tasks distribution
- 4. Code reviews
- 5. Writing web scrappers and CRMs
- 6. Writing discord bots

Technology stack:

- TypeScript
- Node.js, Express.js, Discord.js
- Python + Flask, Discord.py
- PostgreSQL
- RPC interaction: Solana, Ethereum, Tron, Binance Smart Chain

Co-founder, tech leader at Degosh, Moscow, Russia

May 2021 – July 2022

Responsibilities:

- 1. Build backend and frontend architecture
- 2. Reverse engineering, work with captcha and access tokens, TLS servers
- 3. Writing checkout automation bots: supreme, adidas/yeezy, Binance NFT
- 4. Writing and scaling CRM for licenses keys, renewal dates and payments

Technology stack:

- JavaScript, Angular.js
- Node.js, Express.js, Discord.js
- MongoDB
- Webpack

Web developer at Legion-it, Moscow, Russia

June 2019 – October 2020

Responsibilities:

- 1. Developing ecommerce web sites
- 2. Developing landing pages

Technology stack:

- Figma
- WordPress
- Ecwid
- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript, jQuery

Education

Charles university, FSc, Prague, Czech Republic

Drop-out due to the geopolitical situation in Russia, incomplete studying

School 508, Moscow, Russia

Graduated in May 2020

Program of in-depth study of physics and mathematics